{
  "Quiz1": [
    {
      "prompt": "あ",
      "optionA": "i",
      "optionB": "a",
      "optionC": "u",
      "optionD": "o",
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "い",
      "optionA": "i",
      "optionB": "u",
      "optionC": "a",
      "optionD": "o",
      "answer": "i"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "う",
      "optionA": "e",
      "optionB": "o",
      "optionC": "u",
      "optionD": "a",
      "answer": "u"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "え",
      "optionA": "a",
      "optionB": "e",
      "optionC": "i",
      "optionD": "o",
      "answer": "e"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "お",
      "optionA": "u",
      "optionB": "e",
      "optionC": "a",
      "optionD": "o",
      "answer": "o"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "カ",
      "optionA": "he",
      "optionB": "ha",
      "optionC": "ka",
      "optionD": "ma",
      "answer": "ka"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "そ",
      "optionA": "kya",
      "optionB": "so",
      "optionC": "ji",
      "optionD": "sa",
      "answer": "so"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "め",
      "optionA": "ja",
      "optionB": "ju",
      "optionC": "mi",
      "optionD": "me",
      "answer": "me"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ん",
      "optionA": "n",
      "optionB": "o",
      "optionC": "ma",
      "optionD": "ke",
      "answer": "n"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ぞ",
      "optionA": "zo",
      "optionB": "ke",
      "optionC": "ki",
      "optionD": "tsu",
      "answer": "zo"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ぱ",
      "optionA": "pu",
      "optionB": "ke",
      "optionC": "pa",
      "optionD": "ma",
      "answer": "pa"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ぽ",
      "optionA": "ke",
      "optionB": "po",
      "optionC": "pe",
      "optionD": "he",
      "answer": "po"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "ひゅ",
      "optionA": "hyu",
      "optionB": "mya",
      "optionC": "nyu",
      "optionD": "hya",
      "answer": "hyu"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "りょ",
      "optionA": "pyo",
      "optionB": "ryo",
      "optionC": "gyo",
      "optionD": "ryu",
      "answer": "ryo"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "みゅ",
      "optionA": "myu",
      "optionB": "he",
      "optionC": "myo",
      "optionD": "gyu",
      "answer": "myu"
    }
  ]
}